paysec.com 2019-04-09

# Privacy Policy - PaySec

PaySec is fully committed in protecting the security and ensuring the right to privacy of each individual using this website. This is the privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) of PaySec, which explains how we use Personal Information that we collect, receive and store for each user and visitor of [www.paysec.com](http://www.paysec.com/)

Information

1.1 Personal Information. As part of using the services of PaySec, we collect your Personal Information, which can be completed given at your discretion. “Personal Information” means any information that may be used to personally identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, an email address, a home or other physical address, or other contact information. The information you provide allows us to provide an efficient service to you and helps us improve our level of service to better meet your needs.

1.2 Consent. When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, and place an order, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only. By using the Site, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to PaySec processing of Personal Information for the purposes set forth herein. If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime at merchantsupport@paysec.com or mailing us at: 115 B, Suite 3, Old Mint Street, Valleta, VLT 1515, Malta.

Types of information we collect

2.1 Account. To use certain services of www.paysec.com, you may be required to create an Account. By doing so, you will be asked to provide us with mandatory information such as your first name, a user name, email address and a password that you will use for your Account.

2.2. Transfers of Payments. You may be entitled to have us transfer certain amounts of money to you. To the extent that we do so, you will first be required to provide us certain Personal Information regarding your preferred payment method. Such information could include your bank account or credit card name and number.

2.3. Log Files. When you browse the site, we automatically receive your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), and any other information your browser may send to us. We may use this information to analyze and improve accessibility and compatibility of the site, trends, user experience, and gather demographic and statistical information to monitor our services and make it better.

2.4. Cookies. Some of our Site pages utilize “cookies”. A “cookie” may be used, for example, to collect information about Site activity such as but not limited to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc), and record number of visits. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. 

How do we use personal information

All Personal information that you submit or we collect may be used in the following but not limited to:

3.1 Improve our Site, products and services to you, contact you about certain products or services that you may have purchased and registered for, and to authenticate and identify your access of the Site, products and services that you are authorized to access.

3.2 Use your registered external address, email address, mobile or telephone number to send you updates, newsletter, news, promotions regarding the Site and our products and services. Or contact you in response to a “contact us” or “chat with us” request.

3.3 Transfer your Personal Information to our third-party service providers, but only to provide our services to you or for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf.

3.4 We may disclose your Personal Information or any information you submitted if we have a good faith belief that disclosing such information is helpful or reasonably necessary to (i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request; (ii) enforce our Terms of Service including investigations of potential violations thereof; (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud or security issues; or (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of **[www.paysec.com](http://www.paysec.com/)** its users, yourself or the public.

Security and payment

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). All payment-related transactions are encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensures the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

Third-party services

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions. For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner by which these providers will handle your personal information. We are not responsible and expressly exclude ourselves from liability for any damages which may be caused by the privacy practices of such third-party service providers.

Children's privacy

The Site is not structured to offer its products and services or collect information to individuals under the age of 18.

Links

When you click on links on our Site, they may direct you away from our Site. We are not responsible and expressly exclude ourselves from liability for any damages which may be caused by the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements prior to use.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, at our sole discretion, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we provide a notification herein that the same has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our company is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue the services we offer.

Questions and contact information

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information, contact us at [merchantsupport@paysec.com](mailto:merchantsupport@paysec.com).

Return policy

You have thirty (30) calendar days to return any item purchased through this website, from the date you received it.

To be eligible for a return, your item must be unused and in the same condition that you received it. Your item must likewise be in the original packaging and the item needs to have the receipt or proof of purchase.

Once we receive your item, we will inspect it and notify you on your eligibility for a refund and the status thereof.

If your return is approved, we will initiate a refund to the credit card used to purchase the said item. You will receive the credited amount within a certain amount of days, depending on your card issuer’s policies.

The shipping costs for returning your item shall be shouldered by you and is non-refundable. If you receive a refund, the cost of return shipping will be deducted from your refund.
